http://sbhac.ca/privacy-policy/

The Spina Bifida and Hydrocephalus Association of Canada complies with the new privacy legislation, Bill C6, in the following ways:
Collection of Personal Information
The Association collects personal information about you only when you voluntarily provide it, and only for the purpose for which it was intended.
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information
The Association does not sell, rent or trade its membership/donor information to or with others.
Protection and Retention of Personal Information
The Association makes all commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that personal information collected from you is protected against loss and unauthorized access. Access to your personal information is restricted to selected employees or representatives.
We retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws.
Access to Information and Complaints/Withdrawing Consent
You may contact the Association at the address below at any time to: (i) request access to or update or change your personal information; (ii) if you have any questions about this Privacy Statement; (iii) if you have reason to believe that we may have failed to adhere to this Privacy Policy; (iv) if you wish to receive a copy of the Privacy Policy and/or Statement or (v) to request that we remove you from our mailing list.
Send Mail To:
Attn: Privacy Officer
Spina Bifida and Hydrocephalus Association of Canada
472 – 167 Lombard Ave.
Search for:
Donate Today!
In the NewsHydrocephalus
Spina Bifida
Recent Posts
Annual Reports
Notice for Annual General Meeting 2020 (change of date)
Participate in Research – Adolescents and Youth Bloorview Research Institute Research Study
Subscribe to our Newsletter
First name
Email *
